<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on Waldo Ojeda</title>
    <link>http://waldotekampa.me/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on Waldo Ojeda</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2019 Waldo Ojeda</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://waldotekampa.me/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://waldotekampa.me/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://waldotekampa.me/home/about/</guid>
      <description>I am an Assistant Professor in the William Newman Department of Real Estate at the Zicklin School of Business, Baruch College, CUNY. I obtained my Ph.D. in Economics at UC Berkeley. I previously worked in the Household and Real Estate Finance Section at the Federal Reserve Board. I graduated from the University of Chicago in 2010 with a B.A. with Honors in Economics.
Download my CV -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working Papers</title>
      <link>http://waldotekampa.me/home/workingpapers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://waldotekampa.me/home/workingpapers/</guid>
      <description>Common Ownership in the Loan Market
PDF
Firms and banks increasingly have institutional investors as shareholders in common. These shareholders not only receive profits through interest rates, but also benefit from firm profits. In this paper, I first illustrate the implication of firm and bank common ownership on loans in a simple model. I then provide new evidence of the rise and extent of common ownership between firms and banks. I next show that a firm that borrows from a bank with common owners obtains a lower interest rate and a larger loan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Works in Progress</title>
      <link>http://waldotekampa.me/home/worksinprogress/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://waldotekampa.me/home/worksinprogress/</guid>
      <description>Inattention to Earthquake Risk in Home Values I estimate the impact of earthquake risk on residential home prices. Using USGS earthquake hazard map updates, I find that changes in earthquake risk in a county do not impact its house prices. There is no differential impact in counties with ex-ante higher earthquake risk, counties that experience the largest earthquake risk increase or when the updated earthquake risk reaches a level that can cause moderate potential damages to construction when before it did not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>http://waldotekampa.me/home/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://waldotekampa.me/home/teaching/</guid>
      <description>I teach the following course at Baruch College, CUNY:
Undergraduate:
 Real Estate Capital Markets  I was a Graduate Student Instructor for the following courses at UC Berkeley:
Undergraduate:
 Psychology and Economics, Department of Economics  Graduate:
 Corporate Finance, Haas School of Business  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Posts</title>
      <link>http://waldotekampa.me/home/posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://waldotekampa.me/home/posts/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://waldotekampa.me/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://waldotekampa.me/home/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>